Viewers all over the world, I know you are under the influence of my voice.
Where can we go from His voice?
I know you are there for God's promises.
He is faithful; He is not a man. When He says, "Yes", His 'Yes' is 'Yes'.
If He has not promised anything, how can we believe or have faith in Him?
He must promise something; that is why you are there.
He loves you and He is concerned about you.
He is your strength - when you are weak, you are strong.
I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
Whatever situation you are in, never a sickness Jesus cannot heal.
Never a disease Jesus cannot cure.
Never a problem Jesus cannot solve.
Never a burden Jesus cannot bear.
What is your situation?
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
Listen to the voice of God:
"Come unto Me all ye that labour; I will give you rest".
Be released, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
He has said it, "In this world, there will be sickness, burden, affliction - cheer up; I have overcome".
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
What is your situation? This is the voice of God:
There are breakthroughs and there is a breakthrough.
Receive breakthrough, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
A breakthrough that will make you forget the pain of the past -
bitterness, setback, sickness, disease.
Receive breakthrough, in the name of Jesus!
Breakthrough in your health, in the name of Jesus!
Breakthrough in your business, in the name of Jesus!
Breakthrough in your career, in the name of Jesus!
Breakthrough in your family, in the name of Jesus!
A breakthrough in your career!
A breakthrough in your finances!
A breakthrough in your health!
A breakthrough in your future!
Breakthrough!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
I can see you being restored.
That should be your confession right now. Begin to confess your freedom.
I can see you.
Your confession will release the promise of God.
I can see you, right now, being restored.
I can see you being healed.
I can see you being delivered.
I can see you being blessed.
Right now, open your lips and begin to confess your freedom.
Freedom!
I am healed! I am delivered! I am set free! I am saved! Confess your freedom, right now.
Viewers all over the world, begin to confess your freedom.
Confess your freedom.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Viewers, if I had not seen, I would not confess.
I have seen that breakthrough coming.
I have seen that breakthrough coming to you.
I have seen that breakthrough coming to your health, career, finances, future, in Jesus' name.
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.